Guide to the Harris Masterson I papers,1860-1942, bulk 1880-1920 MS 468
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Correspondence, 1882- 1919 (Boxes 59-102)
  - P, 1903 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - R, 1903 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - S, 1903 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - T, 1903 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - V, 1903 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - W, 1903 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Y, 1903 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - A, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - B, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - C, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - D, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - E, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - F, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - G, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - H, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - R.R. Hazelwood, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - I, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - J, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - K, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - L, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - M, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - O, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - P, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - R, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - S, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - T, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Travis L. Smith, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - U-V, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - W, 1904 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - A, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - B, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Banks, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Big Bend Cinnabar Mine, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - C, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - D, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - L.E.L. Duvall, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - E, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - F, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - G, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - R.C. Gaines, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Judge J.M. Gallagher, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - John Giboney, 1905 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - H, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - John Hamman, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - W.M. Hanson, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - R.R. Hazelwood, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Hogg, Watkins Jones, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - J.L. Hudson, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - I, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - J, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Jesse H. Jones, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - K, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - O.H. Kirkland, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - E.N. Krause, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - L, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - C.C. Lastinger, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - M, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - N, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper adverstisement and responses, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Publishers, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Pujo Moss, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - R, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - J.H. Ratcliff, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - J.O. Ross, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Willis J. Roussel, 1905 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - S, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of State [Texas], 1905 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - James B. Chas. J. Stubbs, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Travis L. Smith, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - T.L. Smith, Jr., 1905 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - T, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - U, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - V, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Jas. U. Vincent re: Sour Lake drilling, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - H.C. Voss, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - W, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Lewis J. Wilson, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - A.P. Wooldridge re: City National Bank of Austin, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Y, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - A, 1906 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Association Financiera Internacional, 1906 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - B, 1906 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Banks, 1906 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - C, 1906 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - D, 1906 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Annie P. Doyle, 1906 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - L.E.L. Duvall, 1906 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Willis J. Roussel, 1905 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - F, 1906 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - G, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - John W. Gaines, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Judge J.N. Gallagher, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Claude Gignoux, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - H, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - J.R. Ham, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - C.P. Hampton, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - F.C. Hanford re: Sabine Produce Irrigation Co. stock, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - R.E. Hannay, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Will C. Hogg, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - J.L. Hudson, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - I, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - J, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Jesse H. Jones, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - K, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - S.T. Kerr, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - John H. Kirby, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Obed. H. Kirkland, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Knights and Ladies of Honor, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - E.N. Krause, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - L, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - C.C. Lastinger, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - M, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper advertisement responses, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - P, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Publishers, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Pujo Moss, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Charles D. Pullen, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Joseph R. Putnam, 1906 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - R, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - J.O. Ross, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Willis J. Roussel, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - S, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Salliway McAskill, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of State [Texas], 1906 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Sallie Singleton estate, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Travis L. Smith, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Travis L. Smith, Jr., 1906 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Dan Sullivan Co., 1906 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - John Cotter Sullivan, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - T, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Texas Louisiana Lumber Co., 1906 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - V, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - H.C. Voss, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - W, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Waggoner Title Co., 1906 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Y, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Z, 1906 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - A, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - B, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Banks, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - C, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - D, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Annie P. Doyle, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - L.E.L. Duvall, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - E, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - F, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - G, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Charles S. Gainer, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - R.C. Gaines, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - W.P. Gaines, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Judge J.N. Gallagher, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Claude Gignoux, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - H, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - C.P. Hampton, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - F.C. Hanford re: Sabine Produce Irrigation Co. stock, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Hicks Hicks, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - J.L. Hudson, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Joseph Huffaker, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - J.C. Hutcheson, 1907 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - I, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - J, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Jesse H. Jones, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - K, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - H. Kempner Co., 1907 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - S.G. Kerr, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - John H. Kirby, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Obed. H. Kirkland, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - L, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Jonathan Lane, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - M, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper advertisement responses, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - P, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Publishers, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Pujo Moss, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Charles D. Pullen, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - P.G. Pye Co., 1907 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - R, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - W.G. Ragley, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Raquet Gregg, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Rice Davis, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - W.M. Rice Institute, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Judge R.C. Roper, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - J.O. Ross, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Willis J. Roussel, 1907 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - S (Jan-June), 1907 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - S (July-Dec), 1907 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Salliway McAskill, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of State [Texas], 1907 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Sallie Singleton estate, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - John G. Smith, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Travis L. Smith, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Mrs. Cora B. Stewart, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - John Cutter Sullivan, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - T, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Texas Louisiana Lumber Co., 1907 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - V, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - James U. Vincent re: Sour Lake drilling, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - H.C. Voss, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - W, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Y, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Z, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - A, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - B, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Banks, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - C, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - D, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Annie P. Doyle, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - L.E.L. Duvall, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - E, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - F, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - G, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Charles S. Gainer, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - John W. Gaines, 1908-1909 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - R.C. Gaines, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - W.P. Gaines, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Judge J.N. Gallagher, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Claude Gignoux, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - H, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - W.J. Hamlett, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - R.E. Hannay, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - R.R. Hazelwood, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - R.D. Heatley, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Hicks Hicks, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Hoff, Gill Jones, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - J.L. Hudson, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - I, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - J, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Jesse H. Jones, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - K, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Obed H. Kirkland, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Judge Norman G. Kittrell, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Knights of Honor, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - L, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Lane, Jackson, Kelley Wolters, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - M, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper advertisement responses, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - P, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Publishers, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Charles Pullen, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - R, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - W.G. Ragley, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - O.J. Ramdohr, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - J.H. Rhodes, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - J.S. Rice, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - John Richards, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - J.O. Ross, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - L.H. Rowan, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - S, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Salliway McAskill, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of State [Texas], 1908 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Sallie Singleton estate, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Travis L. Smith, Jr., 1908 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - T, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Texas Louisiana Lumber Co., 1908 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - V, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - W, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Y, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Z, 1908 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - A, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Andrews, Ball Streemon, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - B, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Banks, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - C, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - D, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Annie P. Doyle, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - E, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - F, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Albert B. Fall, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - G, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - John W. Gaines, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - R.C. Gaines, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - H, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - R.E. Hannay, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - R.R. Hazelwood, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - R.D. Heatley, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Will C. Hogg, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - J.L. Hudson, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - I, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - J, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Jesse H. Jones, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - K, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - John H. Kirby, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Obed H. Kirkland, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Norman G. Kittrell, Jr., 1909 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Knights of Honor, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - L, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  - Jonathan Lane, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  - M, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - P, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 31)
  - Publishers, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 32)
  - R, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - W.G. Ragley, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Wm. M. Rice Institute, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - John Richards, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - J.O. Ross, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - S, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Salliway McAskill, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of State [Texas], 1909 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Sallie Singleton estate, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Hampden Storey, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - George H. Sweeney, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - T, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - V, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Velasco Farm Land Co., 1909 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - James U. Vincent re: Sour Lake drilling, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - W, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - H.S.H. Wilson Co., 1909 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Louis J. Wilson, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Y, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Z, 1909 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - A, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - W.M. Andrus, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - B, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Banks, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - C, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - D, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - E, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - F, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - G, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - R.C. Gaines, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - H, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - R.E. Hannay, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Judge J.D. Harvey, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Will C. Hogg, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - J.L. Hudson, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - I, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - J, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Jesse H. Jones, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - K, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Norman G. Kittrell, Jr., 1910 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Knights of Honor, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - L, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - H.M. Lewy, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - M, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Thomas W. Masterson, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - N, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - P, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Publishers, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Pujo Moss, 1910 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - P.G. Pye Co., 1910 (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - R, 1910 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - W.G. Ragley, 1910 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - John Richards, 1910 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - J.O. Ross, 1910 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - S, 1910 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Salliway McAskill, 1910 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of State [Texas], 1910 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Maco Minor Stewart, 1910 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - T, 1910 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Vaughan Hart, 1910 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - James U. Vincent re: Sour Lake drilling, 1910 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - W, 1910 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - H.S.H. Wilson Co., 1910 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Louis J. Wilson, 1910 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Y, 1910 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - A, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Andrews, Ball Streetman, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - W.M. Andrus, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - B, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Banks, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - C, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - D, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - E, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - F, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - G, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - R.C. Gaines, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Egbert J. Gates, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Gill Jones, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - H, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - R.E. Hannay, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - I, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - J, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Jesse H. Jones, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - K, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Norman G. Kittrell, Jr., 1911 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Knights of Honor, 1911 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - L, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Jonathan Lane, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Lea, Bradford Lloyd, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - M, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - N, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - P, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Publishers, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Pujo, Moss Miller, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - P.G. Pye, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - R, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - W.G. Ragley, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - John Richards,1911 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - J.O. Ross, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - S, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of State [Texas], 1911 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Travis L. Smith, Jr., 1911 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - T, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified tenants of Texas Town Lot Improvement Co., 1911 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - V, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - W, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Louis J. Wilson, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Y, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - YWCA YMCA, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Z, 1911 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - A, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Judge A.C. Allen, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Andrews, Ball Streetman, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - W.M. Andrus, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - B, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Banks, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - C, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - D, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - E, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - F, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - G, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Gill Jones, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - H, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - J.L. Hudson, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - I, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - J, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Jesse H. Jones, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - K, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - John H. Kirby, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Judge Norman G. Kittrell, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Norman G. Kittrell, Jr., 1912 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Knights of Honor, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - L, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Lea, Radford Lloyd, 1912 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - M, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - N, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - P, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Publishers, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - R, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - W.G. Ragley, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - O.J. Ramdohr, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - John Richards, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - J.B. Ross, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - J.O. Ross, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - S, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Maco Minor Stewart, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - James B. Charles J. Stubbs, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - J.J. Sweeney, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - T, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified tenants of Texas Town Lot Improvement Co., 1912 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - V, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - W, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Louis J. Wilson, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Y, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - YMCA YWCA, 1912 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - A, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Andrews, Ball Streetman, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - W.M. Andrus, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - H.N. Atkinson, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - B, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Banks, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - C, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - D, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Davis Goggan, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - John L. Dyer, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - E, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - H.H. Everest, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - F, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - G, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - R.C. Gaines, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - H, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - R.E. Hannay, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - J.M. Hansbro, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - John J. Harden, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - F.E. Hunter, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - J.C. Hutcheson, Jr., 1913 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - I, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - J, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Jesse H. Jones, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - K, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Ben Kiam, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Judge Norman G. Kittrell, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Norman G. Kittrell, Jr., 1913 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Knights of Honor, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - L, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Lea, Radford Lloyd, 1913 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - M, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Frank G. Morris, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Publishers, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - I.M. Putnam, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - R, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - W.G. Ragley, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - R.J. Ramdohr, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Wm. M. Rice Institute, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - C.J. Rogers, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - J. Burnett Ross, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - J.O. Ross, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - S, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of State [Texas], 1913 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - J.G. Smith, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Maco Minor Stewart, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - James B. Charles J. Stubbs, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Judge Samuel J. Styles, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - J.J. Sweeney, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - T, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Unidentified tenants of Texas Town Lot Improvement Co., 1913 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - V, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - W, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Louis J. Wilson, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Wilson, Dabney King, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Y, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - YMCA YWCA, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Z, 1913 (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - A, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Andrews, Streetman, Burns Logue, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - H.N. Atkinson, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - B, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Banks, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Brown Terry, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - C, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - D, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - John L. Dyer, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - E, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - H.H. Everest, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - F, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - G, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - John W. Gaines, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - R.C. Gaines, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Gill, Jones Tyler, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - H, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - John J. Harden, 1914 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - I, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - J, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - T.N. Jones re: Allen bankruptcy, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - K, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - H. Kempner, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - R.H. Keyworth, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Judge Norman G. Kittrell, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Norman G. Kittrell, Jr., 1914 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Knights of Honor, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - S.H. Kress Co., 1914 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - L, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Lea, Radford Lloyd, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - M, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Frank G. Morris, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - N, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - W.R. Nash, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - O, 1914 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - E.B. O'Quinn, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - P, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Publishers, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - I.M. Putnam, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Putnam property in OK, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Q, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - R, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - W.G. Ragley, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Rice Bell, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Wm. M. Rice Institute, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - John Richards, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - C.J. Rogers, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - J.O. Ross, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - S, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of State [Texas], 1914 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Maco Minor Stewart, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - James B. Charles J. Stubbs, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Dan Sullivan Co., 1914 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - J.J. Sweeney, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - T, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - V, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - W, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - S.H. Wilson, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Y, 1914 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - A, 1915 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - B, 1915 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Baker, Botts, Parker Garwood, 1915 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - C, 1915 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - L.A. Carlton, 1915 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Cavin Daniels matter, 1915 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Cleveland, 1915 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Emil Cleveland, 1915 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Cravens Cage, 1915 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - D, 1915 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - E, 1915 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - F, 1915 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - G, 1915 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - T.H. Gilliland, 1915 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - H, 1915 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - I, 1915 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - J, 1915 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - K, 1915 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - H. Kempner, 1915 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - M.F. Kirkpatrick re: Cameron Co. property, 1915 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Judge Norman G. Kittrell, 1915 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Knights and Ladies of Honor membership, 1915 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - L, 1915 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - J.T. Loggins, 1915 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - R.B. Loggins, 1915 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - John Lovejoy, 1915 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - J.L. Lubbock, 1915 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - M, 1915 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - McCall, Crawford McCall, 1915 (Box 86, Folder 11)